Are you the kind of person whose desk is always spick and span?
你是那种办公桌总是整洁清爽的人吗？
Or is it a bit of a mess?
还是说你的办公桌有点乱呢？
How you organise your working space can say a lot about you.
你整理工作空间的方式能透露出关于你的很多信息。
In fact, environmental psychologist Lily Bernheimer developed five distinct "desk personality types" in a study commissioned by UK co-working firm Headspace Group.
事实上，环境心理学家莉莉·伯恩海默在英国联合办公公司Headspace Group委托进行的一项研究中，提出了五种不同的“办公桌个性类型”。
Which of them best reflects you?
其中哪一种最能反映出你的性格特征呢？
First up: are you "the clutterer"?
首先：你是“杂乱型”的人吗？
Clutter means mess - and Bernheimer says a clutterer's desk is likely to be colourful, chaotic and covered in trinkets.
“clutter”的意思是杂乱——伯恩海默说，杂乱型的人的办公桌可能色彩丰富、杂乱无章，上面摆满了小玩意儿。
These people are usually more extroverted and welcoming, and love being at the "crossroads" of the office.
这些人通常更外向、热情好客，而且喜欢处于办公室的“中心位置”。
The hitch is that they're often too busy to tidy up after themselves!
问题在于他们常常太忙，以至于没有时间收拾自己的东西！
Or perhaps you're "the minimalist"?
或者也许你是“极简主义型”的人呢？
At the opposite end of the spectrum from clutterers, minimalists have nothing on their desks that is not essential.
与杂乱型的人完全相反，极简主义者的办公桌上没有任何不必要的东西。
These people are usually highly conscientious, disciplined, and just a little bit cautious.
这些人通常非常认真负责、自律，只是有点谨慎。
But that doesn't necessarily mean they are introverts, says Bernheimer - they just like structure.
但伯恩海默说，这并不一定意味着他们是内向的人——他们只是喜欢有条理。
Type three is "the expander".
第三种类型是“扩张型”。
Personal space is very important to them, and it creeps ever outwards, even if this is not a consciously aggressive act.
个人空间对他们来说非常重要，而且这个空间会不断向外延伸，即使这并不是一种有意识的挑衅行为。
Bernheimer says: "They may try to claim more and more territory for themselves by moving their coffee cup and their sandwich out further and further."
伯恩海默说：“他们可能会通过把自己的咖啡杯和三明治越放越远，来为自己占据越来越多的地盘。”
"The personaliser" is our fourth type, and it's quite self-explanatory.
“个性化型”是我们的第四种类型，这一类型不言自明。
These people customise their space with photos, mementos and personal objects.
这些人用照片、纪念品和私人物品来定制他们的空间。
"A simple, stylish or unusual workspace tells people that you're high in the trait called 'openness', which means you're likely to be high in creativity, intellectuality and openness to new experience," says Bernheimer.
伯恩海默说：“一个简洁、时尚或不寻常的工作空间会告诉人们，你在‘开放性’这一特质上得分很高，这意味着你可能具有很高的创造力、智慧，并且乐于接受新的体验。”
And finally, there's "the surveyor".
最后，还有“观察者型”。
These people feel insecure in the middle of the office, and seek out the quieter corners.
这些人在办公室的中间位置会感到没有安全感，于是会寻找更安静的角落。
From an evolutionary perspective, looking for well-protected spots from which to keep an eye out for potential threats makes sense.
从进化的角度来看，寻找有良好保护的地方以便留意潜在的威胁是有道理的。
Surveyors are often introverted, but also highly productive and creative, if given the space and support they need.
观察者型的人通常比较内向，但如果给予他们所需的空间和支持，他们也非常有创造力和工作效率。
Whichever type you are, making personal statements through presentation is deep in our nature, says Sam Gosling, professor of psychology at the University of Texas: "One of the reasons physical spaces, including one's office desks, can be so revealing is that they're essentially the crystallisation of a lot of behaviour over time."
德克萨斯大学的心理学教授山姆·戈斯林说，无论你是哪种类型的人，通过外在的呈现方式来表明个性是我们的天性。“包括办公桌在内的物理空间能如此清晰地反映一个人有许多原因，其中一个原因是物理空间本质上是很多久而久之形成的行为的缩影。”